{
  "voters": [
    {
      "id": 1,
      "firstName": "Lucille",
      "lastName": "Wang",
      "address": "123 Tally St",
      "county": "ABC",
      "city": "East Coast",
      "birthdate": "1915-01-01",
      "email": "lwang@ymail.com",
      "phone": "555-888-0909",
      "completedElectionIds": [
        1
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": 2,
      "firstName": "Evan",
      "lastName": "Hsu",
      "address": "7777 Dead End Rd",
      "county": "ABC",
      "city": "Boise",
      "birthdate": "1915-02-25",
      "email": "fake@gmail.com",
      "phone": "993-765-1234",
      "completedElectionIds": [
        1
      ]
    },
    {
      "firstName": "Mekha",
      "lastName": "Last",
      "address": "laisdfh",
      "county": "Something",
      "city": "Cool City",
      "birthdate": "",
      "email": "a@b",
      "phone": "2983748172",
      "completedElectionIds": [],
      "id": 3
    },
    {
      "firstName": "Tom",
      "lastName": "Philip",
      "address": "dsfsdf",
      "county": "USA",
      "city": "San Diego",
      "birthdate": "",
      "email": "",
      "phone": "",
      "completedElectionIds": [],
      "id": 4
    },
    {
      "firstName": "Tiom",
      "lastName": "",
      "address": "sdfsd",
      "county": "",
      "city": "",
      "birthdate": "",
      "email": "",
      "phone": "",
      "completedElectionIds": [],
      "id": 5
    },
    {
      "firstName": "sdfdsf",
      "lastName": "sdfsd",
      "address": "wfewf",
      "county": "",
      "city": "",
      "birthdate": "",
      "email": "",
      "phone": "",
      "completedElectionIds": [
        1
      ],
      "id": 6
    }
  ],
  "elections": [
    {
      "id": 1,
      "name": "Dinner Poll",
      "questions": [
        {
          "question": "Should I have mexican food for dinner?",
          "responseType": "bool"
        },
        {
          "question": "Should I have dessert?",
          "responseType": "bool"
        },
        {
          "question": "Should I skip dinner?",
          "responseType": "bool"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": 2,
      "name": "Pet Poll",
      "questions": [
        {
          "question": "Should I get a cat?",
          "responseType": "bool"
        },
        {
          "question": "Should I get a dog?",
          "responseType": "bool"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "name": "Cats or Dogs",
      "questions": [
        {
          "question": "Cats?",
          "responseType": "bool"
        },
        {
          "question": "Dogs?",
          "responseType": "bool"
        }
      ],
      "id": 3
    },
    {
      "name": "ice cream",
      "questions": [
        {
          "question": "vanilla",
          "responseType": "bool"
        },
        {
          "question": "choco",
          "responseType": "bool"
        }
      ],
      "id": 4
    },
    {
      "name": "Election3",
      "questions": [
        {
          "question": "Color1",
          "responseType": "bool"
        },
        {
          "question": "Color2",
          "responseType": "bool"
        }
      ],
      "id": 5
    }
  ],
  "ballots": [
    {
      "voterId": 1,
      "electionId": 1,
      "answers": [
        {
          "question": "Should I have mexican food for dinner?",
          "voterResponse": "true"
        },
        {
          "question": "Should I have dessert?",
          "voterResponse": "true"
        },
        {
          "question": "Should I skip dinner?",
          "voterResponse": "false"
        }
      ],
      "id": 1
    },
    {
      "voterId": 2,
      "electionId": 1,
      "answers": [
        {
          "question": "Should I have mexican food for dinner?",
          "voterResponse": "false"
        },
        {
          "question": "Should I have dessert?",
          "voterResponse": "true"
        },
        {
          "question": "Should I skip dinner?",
          "voterResponse": "true"
        }
      ],
      "id": 2
    },
    {
      "voterId": 6,
      "electionId": 1,
      "answers": [
        {
          "question": "Should I have mexican food for dinner?",
          "voterResponse": "false"
        },
        {
          "question": "Should I have dessert?",
          "voterResponse": "true"
        },
        {
          "question": "Should I skip dinner?",
          "voterResponse": "true"
        }
      ],
      "id": 3
    }
  ]
}